

# CONTACT

- 09610298605
- rochenettel@gmail.com
- Alegria, Cebu

# <u>SKILLS</u>

- Figma
- Substance painter
- Quixel Bridge
- Word
- Excel

# **ROCHENETTE LEGASPINA**

**UI/UX** Designer



## **PROFILE**

I am a highly motivated UI/UX Designer committed to continuous learning and self-improvement. With a strong work ethic and passion for design, I focus on creating user-centered experiences while refining my skills. My diverse experience as a System Analyst, UI/UX Designer, and 3D Modeler has strengthened my technical proficiency and problem-solving abilities, enabling me to excel in the design field.



### **EDUCATION**

#### **University of Cebu**

Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering 2016-2021



## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **System Analyst**

Alliance Software Inc. 2023 - Present

#### **UI/UX Designer**

Mach95 Software Development Corporation 2021-2022

#### **3D Modeller**

Exodia Game Development Outsourcing 2019-2021 Contributed to the CASA GORORDO MUSEUM VR project as a 3D Modeller